<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Pals | Posts by Ruben Hillier]]></title>
  <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/categories/pals/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tregeagle.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-09-10T18:16:33+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://tregeagle.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ruben Hillier]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Wilson]]></title>
    <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/2014/11/28/simon-wilson/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-28T20:20:15+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://tregeagle.com/blog/2014/11/28/simon-wilson</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I found a series of photo&rsquo;s on an old back-up a few months ago. Which reminded me of my pal Simon. I&rsquo;m going to post them here so that he can ask me to unpost it.</p>

<p>I am quite an annoying old friend.</p>

<p><img src="/images/photos/2001-Simon_Wilson1.jpg" width="600" title="&lsquo;Simon Wilson 2001&rsquo;" ></p>

<p>I&rsquo;m not quite sure how old I was, perhaps about 14 or 15, when I made friends with Simon Wilson. Without extended family in the immediate vicinity we were outsiders in our village. Tribal sports such as football or rugby did not interest us. We both liked gaming on <a href="http://www.worldofspectrum.org/">ZX Spectrums</a>. We were both a tad geeky, which was not cool back in 1984. It still isn&rsquo;t really, despite what the telly tells you (<a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/big_bang_theory/">Big Bang</a>? Fibs).</p>

<p><img src="/images/photos/2001-Simon_Wilson2.jpg" width="600" title="&lsquo;Simon Wilson 2001&rsquo;" ></p>

<p>We went for cycle rides mostly just to the gravel pits but at least once to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rinsey">Rinsey</a> and on occaison to <a href="http://www.poldark-mine.co.uk/about-us.php">Ha&#8217;penny Park</a>. We explored Lowertown woods with BJ, the Wilson family dog. Simon&rsquo;s little brother sometimes tagged along. We enjoyed discussing and playing computer and board games. Jet Set Willy was my favourite, only because I could &lsquo;hack&rsquo; it with &lsquo;pokes&rsquo; (too boring to explain). The fledgling franchises of The Hobbit, Lord of the Rings and Star Wars all figured strongly.</p>

<p><img src="/images/photos/2001-Simon_Wilson3.jpg" width="600" title="&lsquo;Simon Wilson 2001&rsquo;" ></p>

<p>Like the many friendships throughout my life this one dissolved in time. Now I live on the otherside of the world and never glimpse my old friend, which is a shame.</p>

<p>Wishing you all the best Simon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[CJ]]></title>
    <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/2014/11/18/cj/"/>
    <updated>2014-11-18T14:35:16+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://tregeagle.com/blog/2014/11/18/cj</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>CJ was a friend of mine who died of old age. I say old age but the hospital would tell you it was stroke. CJ would have told you it was because his body betrayed him.</p>

<p><img src="/images/photos/CJ-amongst-the-bitou.jpg" width="360" title="&lsquo;CJ in the beach reserve&rsquo;" > <img src="/images/photos/CJ-amongst-the-bitou-.jpg" width="360" title="&lsquo;getting amongst the bitou bushes&rsquo;" ></p>

<p>After going for a run this morning I climbed down the 74 steps for a morning swim. The water was cold and the waves messy. I ducked, floated and dived before finally letting the waves wash me back in. As I walked back up the steps struggling with my damp t-shirt I thought about CJ. He loved Murrays beach, he pulled out the bitou bushes, to give the native plants a chance, and he picked up the rubbish people left behind. He planted grass and pandanaus palms to stabilise the sand dunes, he wrote many lovely poems about his &lsquo;ancient beach&rsquo;.</p>

<p>I hope his family won&rsquo;t mind if I share one here:</p>

<blockquote><p><strong>My Ancient Beach</strong></p>

<p>The over-arching vault of peerless blue sky.<br/>
The metamorphic tongue of  blackened rock<br/>
lancing the beach of spangling brightness<br/>
to islands beyond the surf,<br/>
now rookeries for  tern and gull.<br/>
The pineappled pandanus standing stark<br/>
its roots tracking nutrients and water<br/>
as it leaches back to the sea.</p>

<p>Crackling waves kiss the beach today<br/>
swirling round the polished pebbles<br/>
which I sample for my Shinto garden.<br/>
The search for tranquility in my life<br/>
comes closer to fruition here<br/>
and like some druid admiring Nature<br/>
I leave offerings by taking rubbish away<br/>
pulling out weeds and starting out <br/>
a host of young pandanus <br/>
to reach out and touch the sky.</p>

<p>CJ</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
