<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Narcissism | Posts by Ruben Hillier]]></title>
  <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/categories/narcissism/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tregeagle.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-09-10T18:16:33+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://tregeagle.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ruben Hillier]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seventeen Months Is a Lifetime]]></title>
    <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/2016/08/25/Seventeen-months-is-a-lifetime/"/>
    <updated>2016-08-25T20:00:39+10:00</updated>
    <id>http://tregeagle.com/blog/2016/08/25/Seventeen-months-is-a-lifetime</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to the <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20010217164613/http://www.tregeagle.com/">Wayback Machine</a> tregeagle.com has been running my blog for over 16 years now. So, maybe not posting anything for almost a year and a half is OK. It&rsquo;s not that I have nothing to say, it&rsquo;s just that I&rsquo;m not sure you need to hear it.</p>

<p>A lot has happened. In short I have left behind my previous life and found a new one. All the old reference points have been rearranged. I&rsquo;ll not dwell on it, you can figure it out.</p>

<p><a href="http://microblog.ourcoffs.org.au/conversation/171943"><img alt="Red Wedge 1918" src="images/pictures/redwedge.jpg"></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks Mr White]]></title>
    <link href="http://tregeagle.com/blog/2015/03/26/andy-white/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-26T20:58:39+11:00</updated>
    <id>http://tregeagle.com/blog/2015/03/26/andy-white</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;ve been ramping up my running lately. It&rsquo;s a type of meditation. Sometimes I just run. Other times I run and listen to music or podcasts.</p>

<p>Yesterday I went for a <dfn title="Trying to increase my speed for the Gold Coast Marathon">tempo run</dfn> in the rain. I listened to the album, &ldquo;<a href="http://www.andywhite.com/album/rave-on-andy-white/" title="Go buy a copy from himself">Rave On Andy White</a>&rdquo; and entered my usual running dream/pain state. I thought of the inspirations I attached to these songs over the years. I thought how those inspirations morph into reminders. Sometimes they are just reminders about the stupid things I used to get inspired about. Other times I am reminded about the type of person I wanted to be.</p>

<iframe width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/VPxuEYR8908?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>Andy White sung about <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xzxhpZYO19Y" title="maybe he is right?">Reality Row</a> like it was a bad thing. Maybe he is right?</p>

<p>I think he rather fancied himself as a &lsquo;WockStah&rsquo; as he walked down <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=12rnbGw9kAk" title="The middle of the road is apparently not as cool as six string street">Six String Street</a> in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x4qooN-uzA8" title="Andy sings about groovy stuff on YTube">Groovy Kind of Way</a>. Despite Andy being a bit of a narcissistic wanker I&rsquo;ve always loved his cheerful tunes. Show me someone without a crazy self-centred dream and I&rsquo;ll show you a dull ass. Andy liked to pretend to be some sort of romantic version of Bob Dylan or an Irish version of Billy Bragg, some say he is. I wore out several of his cassette tapes over the years and I always love rediscovering his pop-with-a-hint-of-politics but mostly silly-romantic. Which probably about sums me up.</p>

<p>Here is a picture of me in the midst of a depressing and life changing time in 1990-ish.</p>

<p><img src="/images/photos/ruben-ponty.jpg" width="760" title="&lsquo;Ruben depressed in Pontypridd, Wales. Circa 1990-1&rsquo;" ></p>

<p>I was probably recently returned from or soon to go to one of the many music festivals around at the time. I remember the Fleadh at Finsbury Park and the Féile in Tipperary. I am sure I was listening to Andy White when Neil, Gareth or Lizzy snapped it.</p>

<p>So, the run was shit. I could barely walk to the bog last night. Andy, as always, was good company on my crap journey. He helped me crack open a few insights along the way. Thanks for that Mr White.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
